# MAR JOHN CORNELIO

# **Junior Web Developer**

**\** +63-916-826-9678

mc.marjohncornelio@gmail.com

https://github.com/mjcornelio

San Jose Del Monte, Bulacan

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/marjohn-cornelio

# **SUMMARY**

Web developer with a passion for creating engaging user experiences. Graduate of the Bachelor of Science in Information Technology program at Bulacan State University - Sarmiento Campus. Proficient in Front-end and Back-end web development with experience using the latest libraries and frameworks.

# **EXPERIENCE**

### 07/2023 - Present

Quezon City, Philippines

# Junior Web Developer

#### **PAPH Travel and Tours**

PAPH Travel and Tours offers a wide range of travel packages, including flight bookings, hotel reservations, and exciting tour options to various destinations.

- Contributed in the development of a booking web-based system using React.js, Material UI, and Redux, catering to a global audience.
- Collaborated closely with the team to implement user interface designs and seamlessly integrate
  APIs using NodeJs, ExpressJS and .NET for travel booking functionalities.

#### 01/2023 - 04/2023

San Jose del Monte, Bulacan

### IT Associate - Internship

#### **Qualimed Hospital**

QualiMed Hospital is the first hospital-format facility in Luzon under the QualiMed Health Network, which is operated and owned by MGHI and Ayala Land, Inc.

- Assist in the management of an IT infrastructure of an organization as well as providing technical support for computer systems and troubleshooting issues encountered by end users
- Assigned to create a Helpdesk Ticketing System using React.js, Node.js, Express.js and MySQL.

### **EDUCATION**

2019 - 2023

San Jose del Monte, Bulacan

# Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Magna Cum Laude

### **Bulacan State University - Sarmiento Campus**

- Develop a property rental management system for a local business using React.js, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, Sequelize, and XAMPP for the Capstone Project.
- Deans Lister, Best in web development awardee. Finished with GWA of 1.35

# **SKILLS**

# Web Development

- Proficient in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Familiar in JavaScript framework such as React.js.
- Skilled in implementing front-end libraries and frameworks like Bootstrap and Material UI.
- Familiar in server-side language and database management like Node.js, ExpressJS and MySQL

### Programming Fundamentals

- Basic understanding with a variety of programming languages including Java, Python, and C#.
- Familiar in version control and collaboration using Git and GitHub.

### Technical Support

- Technical knowledge of computer hardware, software, and networking
- Ability to provide technical support and troubleshoot issues for end-users.

# **CHARACTER REFERENCE**

Available upon Request.